### Contact

kgilroy102068@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/karmenrobinson-77a90bbb (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

**Team Building** 

Nursing

Interpersonal Communication

#### Certifications

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Interpersonal Communication
Inpatient Obstetric Nursing (RNC)

**Fetal Monitoring** 

NRP

# Karmen Robinson

BSN, RNC-OB

Savannah, Georgia Area

## Summary

25 years Nursing experience in Women's and Infant Care as a staff nurse, charge nurse, and manager. Presently pursuing my Master's Degree in Nursing Informatics to become an authentic APRN and educate nurses of the future in evidence based practice and compassionate patient care.

## Experience

Liberty Regional Medical Center Registered Nurse Newborn Nursery December 2019 - Present (7 months) Hinesville, Georgia, United States

Nurse First Travel Agency Travel Nurse October 2019 - December 2019 (3 months)

Republic Health Resources
Travel Nurse
June 2017 - September 2019 (2 years 4 months)

IPI Travel
Travel Nurse
December 2014 - June 2017 (2 years 7 months)

Trinity Hospital of Augusta Charge Nurse October 2003 - October 2014 (11 years 1 month) Labor and Delivery

### Education

Western Governors University

MSN , Nursing Informatics · (2020 - 2022)

University of South Alabama College of Nursing Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1992 - 1995)

Phillips Junior College
Medical/Clinical Assistant · (1991 - 1992)